http://www.tote-betting.net/privacy-policy.php

Live Online Horseracing
One of the more recent innovations to the services offered by the online bookmakers is that if you bet with any of the online bookmakers offering the Live Horse racing service you can watch the race you bet on live on your computer.Watch Live Racing
Tote Bets Guide
Tote Win Betting
Tote Place Bets
Tote Exacta Betting
Tote Scoop6 Betting
Tote Placepot Bets
Tote Quadpot Guide
Tote Jackpot Betting
Tote Trifecta Guide
Privacy Policy
Tote Betting (hereafter referred to as 'we' and 'us') are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, our Cookies Policy, please do not use or submit information to us via our website. This policy was last updated on 1st May 2018.
Tote Betting is not a bookmaker or gaming company but an affiliate to the sites we choose to promote. We are located in the UK and all our partner sites are UK licensed or licensed in a location where gambling is permitted.
Website Administration
Business Name : Moneta Communications Ltd
Address : Tower House, Parkstone Road, Poole, Dorset
Post Code : BH15 2JH
Country : England
Website URL : http://www.tote-betting.net
Tel: 0161 507 9888
For the purpose of the data protection legislation (including the Data Protection Act 1998) the data controller is Moneta Communications Limited.
Information We Collect
We collect information about you when using this website. The information is collected when you use our website and interact with our products and services. We never sell or give away this information.
Information we get from your device
We collect information from your device when using our site. Examples of information we collect, but are not limited to, are IP address, device model, version, operating system, software version, preferred language and location data.
We also collect server logs information such as date and time of site use, app features or pages you view, site/app crashes and third-party sites or services used directly before visiting our site.
Publicly Available Information
Whenever we are required to assist with or settle any concerns, disputes or situations where extensive research has to be undertaken, we may look at publicly available information about you such as social media accounts. Although this information is public, we remain mindful of your privacy and use it only as and where necessary for carrying out these checks.
Information We Get From Social Media
If you raise a concern or complaint through Tote Betting Facebook or Twitter accounts we do not store your username, however we may look at your Facebook or Twitter information to help resolve the concern or complaint.
We use information posted publicly on social media to help us understand how our customers interact with us and we use this information to help us improve our products and services to you. We do this in a way that does not identify you as an individual.
Providing Our Products And Services
There are certain things we have to do in order to be able to provide our products and services to you. We use information we get from your device to help us to make decisions on how to improve our products and service to you, as well as ensuring you have the latest versions of our site.
How Long Do We Keep Your Information?
We will not hold your personal information for any longer than is necessary for functions on our website. We will review our databases on a periodic basis and shall delete data which we reasonably believe to be outdated, inaccurate, or no longer necessary. We reserve the right to contact users in respect of this process.
Security Of Personal Data
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Accessing Your Personal Data
You have the right to request a copy of your personal information from us. To do this, you must contact us directly and we will need to perform data validity checks to clarify valid proof of identity. Please allow time for this process to be completed, however we aim for completion in the shortest time possible.
Your Right To Erasure
You have the right to request erasure of your personal data. This can be sometimes referred to as the 'right to be forgotten'. To do this, you must contact us directly and we will need to perform data validity checks to clarify valid proof of identity. Please allow time for this process to be completed, however we aim for completion in the shortest time possible.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policy applicable to the website in question.
Conflict Resolution
We will endeavour to resolve disputes within 72 hours. If problems arise, users may contact us via the phone number stated above.
This Site Uses Cookies
As is common practice with most websites, this site uses cookies. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser to enable us to recognise your device when you visit our site. They are often used as a mechanism for websites to remember things that a website browser has done there in the past, for example, clicking on particular buttons, logging in, or having previously read pages on the site. This Cookies Policy describes what information we gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade certain elements of the sites functionality.
We may revise and update this Cookies Policy at any time. Please periodically review the Cookies Policy, as your continued use of our site indicates your agreement with any changes that we make.
How We Use Cookies
We use cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately, in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave on all cookies if you are not sure whether you need them or not in case they are used to provide a service that you use.
Types of Cookies
This site uses cookies that are strictly necessary for the performance of the site. These are essential in allowing you to move around the site and log in to secure areas, as well as ensuring the site works properly on your device. Without these cookies, key features of the site will not work properly, and some may not work at all.
Functionality cookies are used to improve the functional performance of the website and make it easier for you to use. These cookies remember choices you have made on site such as your log in information, allowing you to stay logged in on your next visit and as you navigate around our site. They also allow us to show you related content based on your preferences, which you can edit in your profile if you have registered a free account.
Analytical cookies are used to monitor the performance of our site. These collect information about how our site is being used which allows us to review and improve our products and services. In some cases we use cookies provided by trusted third parties. Google Analytics, which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solutions on the web, is used to help us understand how our site is used and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content. For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.
Other third-party analytics are used in a similar way, to track and measure usage of this site so that we can continue to produce engaging content.
From time to time we test new features and make subtle changes to the way that the site is delivered. This means new cookies may be added to the site that are not listed in this Cookies Policy. When we are still testing new features, these cookies may be used to ensure that you receive a consistent experience whilst on the site and ensure we understand which optimisations our users appreciate the most.
Several partners advertise on our behalf and use affiliate tracking cookies. These simply allow us to see if you have come to the site through one of our partner sites so that we can credit them appropriately, and where applicable allow our affiliate partners to provide any bonus that they may provide you for making a purchase.
We also use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with your social network in various ways. For these to work, social media sites such as Facebook and Twitter will set cookies through our site which may be used to enhance your profile on their site or contribute to the data they hold for various purposes outlined in their respective privacy policies.
Hopefully that has clarified things for you and as was previously mentioned if there is something that you aren't sure whether you need or not it's usually safer to leave cookies enabled in case it does interact with one of the features you use on our site. However, if you are still looking for more information then you can contact us via the phone number stated above.
Disabling Cookies
You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser 'Help' for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of this site. Therefore, it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.
Horse Racing Results & Tote Dividends
Our live horse racing results service provides todays uk racing results as they happen and also an archive of past results day by day. Our results service provides the latest winners and placed horses along with their starting price, tote dividends and also the tote exacta and where applicable the trifecta.Live UK Horse Racing ResultsOur tote betting service and horse racing guide also lists the latest free bets on offer with the main uk bookmakers. Each offer is updated on a daily basis, both for bookmakers free tote bets and also free general sports betting.
Tote Scoop6 Betting & Results
Probably the most publicised tote bet as it is run each Saturday and the objective is to pick the 6 winners of each of the selected races that make up the Scoop 6 on that day. The Scoop 6 races usually are the races shown on terrestrial TV so as to give it the biggest viewership and audience.Tote Scoop6 Betting Guide
Tote Scoop6 Betting Result 14th December 2019Scoop6 Win Fund Total:£186,599.70Scoop6 Place Fund Total:£36,523Scoop6 Bonus Fund Total:£212,519Tote Scoop6 Results for 14th December 2019
How to place a bet on the Tote Scoop6Past Tote Scoop6 Results & Pool Dividends Tote Placepot Betting & Results
The tote Placepot has captured the imagination of the punting public and this is without doubt one of the most played tote bets. For those who wish to have an interest in the afternoons racing the Placepot provides the ideal bet to keep you involved throughout the day.Tote Placepot Betting Guide
Tote Placepot Results and Dividends - 19th December
CoursePlacepotExeter1.70
Hereford13.60
Southwell20.50
Wolverhampton347.50
Tote Placepot Results and Totepool Dividends
View our Privacy Policy
We are committed to supporting Responsible Gambling Initiatives - For additional information visit : GamCare | Gamble Aware | Gamblers Anonymous
